massivead.com 2014-07-03

# Privacy Policy - Massive Ad

Protecting your privacy is the main priority at Massive Ad World-Wide We is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information while stored in our electronic facility. Any personal information provided to us, collected by us or stored in our facility is not accessible by anyone but you through the use of your unique user name and password. In the performance of our duty, only a limited number of system administrators have monitored access to the information that you provide while purchasing our product and/or services. When you solicit our service, we tell you about this policy and obtain your consent before collecting, using or disclosing personal information, except where permitted or allowed by law. 

## BINDING EFFECT

The Massive Ad Privacy Policy applies to EVERYONE at Massive Ad World-Wide, INCLUDING YOU, OUR CUSTOMER. YOU HEREBY SWEAR THAT YOU ARE AT LEAST 18 OF AGE AND CAPABLE TO ENTER INTO A BINDING CONTRACT. YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE CONSTITUTES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND ANY SUBSEQUENT MODIFICATIONS THERETO. IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DISCONTINUE YOUR USE OF THE MASSIVE AD WEBSITE. 

## COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

When you register with Massive Ad World-Wide, you supply personal information, this includes your email address that is required to open an account with us. We limit the personal information we collect to what is necessary for the purpose of our business. We obtain information about you for identification purposes. This is done to protect both you and Massive Ad against error and fraud, to monitor traffic to our Website, to understand your usage of our product and services, to contact you and recommend particular products and services that meet your needs, to provide you with ongoing service, to respond to customer inquiries and comments, to maintain a list of Massive Ad World-Wide customers and to comply with legal requirements. 

After registering with Massive Ad World-Wide, you may cancel your account at any time. Minimum personal information allowing Massive Ad World-Wide to track a cancelled customer for the reason of verification or other official reasons, such as and where required by law, will be kept for a period of three years after a cancellation occurring after registration. To cancel a registration you need to follow necessary steps mentioned in our refund/cancellation policy. 

Massive Ad World-Wide will not use or disclose collected personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with your express consent or if required by law. By providing personal information to Massive Ad World-Wide, you agree and consent to the collection, use and/or disclosure of such information by Massive Ad World-Wide for the purposes stated above. 

## TYPES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect necessary identification information, including Names, Address, Birth Date, Occupation and Citizenship. To verify the authenticity of Citizenship, we require at least one government issued ID number. We do collect financial information such as Credit Card information or Bank Account information for the purpose of paying commissions. 

## PROTECTING, MAINTAINING ACCURATE, AND PROVIDING YOU ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION

We safeguard the privacy of your personal information through appropriate security measures. We make sure personal information is as accurate, complete and up-to-date as necessary. At your request, we provide you full access to your personal information. You can inquire about its use and disclosure, you can verify whether it is accurate and complete and modify it if necessary. If doing so personally it will not compromise Massive Ad World-Wide's privacy or security interests. Our Policies and Practices regarding the management of your personal information is made available to you so that you know what steps you can follow if you have concerns or questions about your privacy. There are designated agents in our company who have access to your personal information in conjunction to their professional duties. These individuals are asked to sign strict confidentiality and non-disclosure agreements to ensure their compliance with legal requirements in relation to the handling of affiliate information. We monitor their compliance with applicable privacy legislations. 

## TRANSFERRING OR SHARING YOUR INFORMATION

Massive Ad World-Wide does not sell or otherwise transfer personal information to unaffiliated third parties except where you specifically authorize us to do so. Unless prohibited by law, Massive Ad World-Wide does however share information with its affiliates, subsidiaries and even third parties providing services on behalf of Massive Ad World-Wide, Massive Ad Reseller, the Monetize Group, its affiliates or subsidiaries for the purpose of allowing all the above entities to bring suitable products and services to your attention or upon you request. You can choose to oppose the sharing of your information within our group and your given consent can be withdrawn any time, unless legal requirements prevent it. From time to time, Massive Ad World-Wide, its affiliates, subsidiaries or third parties working on our behalf may offer you products and services - including special promotions - that we believe will be of interest to you through direct mail, telephone, e-mail or other means. If you do not wish to be included in Massive Ad World-Wide or Massive Ad World-Wide's future marketing efforts, or if you would like to have your personal information removed from our direct marketing database, please notify Massive Ad World-Wide by e-mail at support@Massivead.com 

## DISCLOSURE OF GENERAL AND ANONYMOUS INFORMATION

Massive Ad World-Wide will, at times, conduct market research such as investigations and the statistical analyses of anonymous and aggregated customer information and other service related information, in order to measure interest in the Website or other related factors and parameters. Massive Ad World-Wide reserves the right to publish, share, transfer or sell results of such general and anonymous researches and analyses to third parties. 

## PROTECTING YOUR INFORMATION

Massive Ad World-Wide is obligated to protect your personal information by making reasonable security arrangements against such risks as loss, misuse, unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or disposal/destruction. Several physical, electronic and procedural security measures have been integrated into the day-to-day operating practices of our company to safeguard the personal information you provide us. This includes the use of appropriate technology to process all traffic at this website. We use several layers of robust security methods among which, SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology, encryption, firewalls and timed log-outs among others to ensure the confidentiality of your personal information. 

  * SSL (Secure Socket Layer Technology) is the standard tool for protecting and maintaining security over the Internet. Ensure your connection is secure by looking for either a 'closed lock' or an 'unbroken key' icon located at the bottom right hand side of your browser's task bar. 

  * Encryption scrambles your data into an unreadable format to block unauthorized access by others. 

  * Timed log-outs are destined to automatically terminate a session after a period of inactivity just in case you forget to log out or leave a computer unattended during an online session. 

## PASSWORD

Access to your personal information posted on our Website will be password protected. You are responsible for keeping your password confidential in order to prevent unauthorized access. You agree to promptly notify Massive Ad World-Wide of any unauthorized use of your password. You will be liable for any orders placed with or any electronic data provided to Massive Ad World-Wide until Massive AdWorld Wide is notified of an unauthorized use of your password. 

Never disclose your current passwords or answers to online personal. No Massive Ad World-Wide employee or agent will ever ask you verbally or through e-mail for this information. 

However, if for some reason you cannot access your account and ask us to help you, we may ask for some predetermined security words to identify you. 

## LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

The content of our Website may contain links to third party Websites. This privacy statement applies only to Massive Ad World-Wide and The Monetize Group for information collected by these two companies. It does not apply to any third-party Websites you access from our Website, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. It is your responsibility to be aware of and comply with such privacy policies. 

## E-MAIL

Massive Ad World-Wide will not monitor, edit, or disclose private communications unless: (i) required to do so by law; (ii) you grant us permission; or (iii) in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law; (b) comply with any legal process that is served on Massive Ad World-Wide; or (c) protect and defend the rights or property of Massive Ad World-Wide 

## COOKIES

A cookie is a computer code that lets Web servers "identify" visitors to the Website. Every time you start a session on the Massive Ad World-Wide Website, our server uses a cookie to identify you as the account holder and provides you with appropriate access privileges. Cookies do not store any of the personal information you have provided through the site; they are simply identifiers. Cookies collect information such as your browser type, time and length of your visit. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can choose to refuse cookies, or selectively accept cookies, by adjusting the preferences in your browser. However, if you refuse cookies, some features of our site will not be available to you and some Web pages may not display properly. 

## EFFECTIVE DATE

This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 12th 2013. Massive Ad World-Wide reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by notifying you of the existence of a new Privacy Policy. Such changes, modifications, additions or deletions shall be effective immediately upon notice thereof, which may be given by means including, but not limited to, posting on the Website, or by any other means by which you obtain notice thereof. Your continued use of the Website after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. 

## SEVERABILITY

If any provision of this Policy shall be held to be invalid, illegal or unenforceable, the validity, legality and enforceability of the remaining provisions shall not in any way be affected or impaired thereby, and such illegal or unenforceable provision shall be interpreted, construed, or reformed to the extent reasonably required to render it valid, enforceable and deemed to be restated to reflect the original intentions of the drafter of this Privacy Policy as nearly as possible in accordance with applicable law(s). 

## CONTACTING MASSIVE AD

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of Massive Ad World-Wide in respect of this Website, please direct your inquiry directly to Massive Ad World-Wide by writing to support@massivead.com Massive Ad World-Wide will investigate promptly and try everything possible to resolve complaints or disputes related to the use and disclosure of Consumers' personal information in accordance to this Privacy Policy and all applicable laws. 

This is a living document, which means that when circumstances dictate, this document will be updated. When this is done, the latest version will be updated on the Massive Ad website, and the latest version Date will be updated accordingly
